Office of the Dean of Graduate Studies fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
Office of the Dean of Graduate Studies fonds
1965 - 2000
F-225
4.5 m of textual records
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department Maggie Benston Student Services Building, Rm. 0400 8888 University Dr. Burnaby British Columbia Canada V5A 1S6 Telephone: 778.782.3805 Email: archives@sfu.ca http://www.sfu.ca/archives
The predominant dates for this fonds are 1965-1998. Records dating post-1998 are all found in Series 7 (Publications) and date 1990 - 2000.
Financial assistance for the arrangement and description of the records and production of the finding aid was generously provided by the Office of the Dean of Graduate Studies in 2006.
Office of the Dean of Graduate Studies
When SFU opened in 1965 the Board of Governors and senior academic staff agreed that there were not enough students to form a separate faculty of Graduate Studies. For the first couple of years, each academic department was responsible for the administration of their own graduate students and the development of graduate programs. In 1968 the Senate Committee on Graduate Studies approved the formation of departmental graduate studies committees and the recommendation of a Dean of Graduate Studies. In 1971, the Office of the Dean of Graduate Studies was officially created. Reporting to the Vice-President, Academic, the Dean was given responsibility for graduate studies policy development and graduate student services, including the administration of research and grants for faculty and scholarships for students. In 1994 the Dean's role was combined with that of Vice-President, Research with the graduate studies portfolio reporting to the Vice-President, Academic. In 2000 the Dean of Graduate Studies was made a separate position once again, with the Vice-President, Research taking responsibility for research administration and the Dean of Graduate Studies reporting back again to the Vice-President, Academic and Provost.
The Office of the Dean of Graduate Studies ensures that graduate students throughout the university conform to standards approved by the university Senate. The Dean is assisted by an Associate Dean of Graduate Studies who is responsible for matters that involve individual students and individual graduate programs. The Dean retains primary responsibility for policy matters and external relations. The Dean approves supervisory committees, recommends the awarding of degrees, advises on program development and approves new graduate programs. The Dean also administers and provides information about all graduate awards and liaises with national and provincial granting agencies. The Office of the Dean of Graduate Studies maintains all formal graduate student records from the time of application to the awarding of degrees. The Dean's office also administers Special Arrangement students and Post-doctoral Fellows. The Office of the Dean of Graduate Studies organizes a number of events throughout the year including Graduate Scholarships Day, the TA/TM Day, library workshops for graduate students, SFU Graduate Student Certificate Program in University Teaching and Learning, and the SFU Teaching, Learning, and Research Showcase.
The Dean of Graduate Studies participates in university administration through membership on senate and various senate committees. The Dean serves as Chair of the Senate Graduate Studies Committee, the Executive Committee of the Senate Graduate Studies Committee, the Assessment Committee for New Graduate Programs, the University Ethics Review Committee, the Senate Graduate Awards Adjudication Committee, and the President's Research Grant Committee. The Dean serves as an ex officio member of Senate, the Senate Committee on Academic Planning, and the Senate Policy Committee for Scholarships, Awards and Bursaries. Over the years, the Dean of Graduate Studies has also served on a series of external boards, including the TRIUMF (Tri-University Meson Facility) Board of Management, the Canadian Association for Graduate Studies, and the Western Canadian Deans of Graduate Studies Committee.
published
Full
Published
The title of the fonds is based on the name of the creating body.
The fonds consists of records relating to the administration of the Office of the Dean of Graduate Studies. Activities, topics and events documented include the Dean's correspondence with graduate program chairs and academic departments, the greater university community, student clubs, and provincial and national organizations; participation on external and university committees; review of new graduate programs; planning and delivery of training programs and workshops; and the adjudication of graduate scholarships, awards, and bursaries.
The types of documents include meeting agendas, minutes, and supporting papers; correspondence and reports; annual reports; budgets and financial working papers; contracts; new graduate program reviews; and publications including graduate program brochures, student handbooks, and newsletters.
The finding aid for F-225 replaces the superceded/obsolete finding aid for F-21, Office of the Dean of Graduate Studies. Please consult an Archivist for file references that refer to old F-21 numbers.
The material was arranged by the Archivist as no original file arrangement or classification plan was identified during processing. Within each series the records have been arranged chronologically.
Driver, Jonathan; Hart, Stephen D.; Martin, Jack; Wrenn, Phyllis; Heift, Trude; Clayman, Bruce P.; Bowman, Marilyn L.; Webster, John M.; Doerr, Audrey D.; Curtis, Jared R.; Beirne, Bryan P.; Blackman, Roger; Wheatley, Jon; Rieckhoff, Klaus E.
The records were transferred to Archives through the regular application of university Records Retention Schedules and Disposal Authorities (RRSDAs).
All accessions have been processed as of September 2006. Further accruals are expected.
For further records relating to the development and administration of the Office of the Dean of Graduate Studies, please refer to the finding aids for the Office of the President (F-193); the Office of the Vice-President, Academic and Provost (F-200); the Office of the Vice-President, Finance and Administration (F-28); and the Senate fonds (F-84). Virtually every academic department at SFU has records relating to graduate studies within their own department. Please consult these individual finding aids for more information.
Some files may contain personal or confidential information. Access to these files may be restricted as required by law. Files marked 'pending review' must be reviewed by an archivist prior to release, and as a result of the review access restrictions may apply. Please see the file lists and consult the archivist for more details.
A file list is available.
Appendix 1 contains the document "Organizational Structure of Graduate Studies at SFU" and Appendix 2 contains "Office of the Dean of Graduate Studies" which describes the role and responsibilities of the Dean. Both documents can also be found on the Dean of Graduate Studies website, http://www.sfu.ca/dean-gradstudies/.
- Dean's administrative records, 1968 - 1998; F-225-1; 71 cm of textual records
  published
  Series consists of records relating to the administration of the Office of the Dean of Graduate Studies. Activities, events and topics documented include a history of Graduate Studies and the Special Arrangements (SAR) program; graduate fees and admissions regulations; development of the graduate student trainee programs; graduate enrollment projections and graduate program reviews; organization of the Graduate Scholarships Day, Awards Day, and T.A. Day; graduate student surveys; and development of the Graduate Studies fact book, newsletter and student handbook. Records include correspondence and working papers, reports, statistics, financial working papers, minutes, and newsletters.
  For copies of the Graduate Studies Handbook and Graduate Studies Fact Book, see series 7, "Publications".
  - Patent policies - SFU, 1968 - 1972; F-225-1-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 225-1)
    Textual records
    Pending review
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-2-1-0-31.
  - Dean of Graduate Studies (history), 1968 - 1980; F-225-1-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 225-1)
    Open
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-12-0-0-16.
  - Copyright: register and assignment of copyright, 1970 - 1973; F-225-1-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 225-1)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-2-1-0-30.
  - Graduate regulations, 1970 - 1973; F-225-1-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 225-1)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-12-0-0-15.
  - Graduate student traineeship program, 1971 - 1974; F-225-1-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 225-1)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-10-0-0-1.
  - A history of Special Arrangements (SAR) at SFU, 1971 - 1990; F-225-1-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 225-1)
  - Bonneau/Corry report (to AUCC), 1972 - 1974; F-225-1-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 225-1)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-2-1-0-1.
  - Graduate requirements - extended essays, 1973 - 1975; F-225-1-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 225-1)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-5-0-0-1.
  - Graduate Student Union/Canadian Union of Graduate Students, 1973 - 1975; F-225-1-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 225-1)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-2-1-0-20.
  - Graduate student traineeship program - budget, 1974; F-225-1-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 225-1)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-10-0-0-2.
  - Ph.D. in Chemistry, 1974; F-225-1-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 225-1)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-2-1-0-42.
  - Graduate student traineeship program, 1974 - 1975; F-225-1-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 225-1)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-10-0-0-3.
  - Graduate student traineeship program - miscellaneous, 1974 - 1978; F-225-1-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 225-1)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-2-1-0-37.
  - Simon Fraser funding statistics, 1974 - 1985; F-225-1-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 225-2)
  - Graduate faculty (draft proposal), 1975; F-225-1-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 225-2)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-2-1-0-8.
  - Political Science Department problems, 1975 - 1982; F-225-1-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 225-2)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-2-3-0-22.
  - Graduate enrollment, 1975 - 1984; F-225-1-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 225-2)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-2-3-0-11.
  - Graduate Awards Clerk, 1975 - 1986; F-225-1-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 225-2)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-2-3-0-10.
  - Future of Graduate Studies at SFU, 1976; F-225-1-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 225-2)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-2-1-0-32.
  - Assessment of existing programs, 1976 - 1979; F-225-1-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 225-2)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-2-1-0-39.
  - Student film copyright agreement, 1977; F-225-1-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 225-2)
  - External examiners, 1977 - 1981; F-225-1-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 225-2)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-7-0-0-1.
  - Enrollment statistics to 1985, 1977 - 1985; F-225-1-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 225-2)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-2-3-0-5.
  - Joint Ph.D. proposal between Faculty of Education and UVic, 1978 - 1980; F-225-1-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 225-2)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-2-3-0-16.
  - Task Force on Faculty Organization, 1979 - 1980; F-225-1-0-0-25 (Archival box - standard 225-2)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-2-3-0-31.
  - Teaching credits for graduate students, 1979 - 1980; F-225-1-0-0-26 (Archival box - standard 225-2)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-2-3-0-33.
  - Special programs for Chinese scholars, 1979 - 1981; F-225-1-0-0-27 (Archival box - standard 225-2)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-2-3-0-30.
  - Professional programs, vol. 1, 1979 - 1981; F-225-1-0-0-28 (Archival box - standard 225-2)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-2-3-0-23.
  - Professional programs, vol. 2, 1979 - 1981; F-225-1-0-0-29 (Archival box - standard 225-3)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-2-3-0-24.
  - Graduate Studies Program - DLLL, 1979 - 1981; F-225-1-0-0-30 (Archival box - standard 225-3)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-2-3-0-14.
  - Organization of faculties, 1979 - 1981; F-225-1-0-0-31 (Archival box - standard 225-3)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-2-3-0-20.
  - Personnel - Assistant to the Dean, 1979 - 1983; F-225-1-0-0-32 (Archival box - standard 225-3)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-2-3-0-21.
  - Graduate fees to 1984, 1979 - 1985; F-225-1-0-0-33 (Archival box - standard 225-3)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-2-3-0-12.
  - Grantsmanship, 1980; F-225-1-0-0-34 (Archival box - standard 225-3)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-2-3-0-15.
  - Theses and abstracts binding, 1980 - 1984; F-225-1-0-0-35 (Archival box - standard 225-3)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-2-2-0-1.
  - SCAP - academic program descriptions, 1981; F-225-1-0-0-36 (Archival box - standard 225-3)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-2-3-0-28.
  - Library Assistant, 1981; F-225-1-0-0-37 (Archival box - standard 225-3)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-2-1-0-5.
  - Graduate program reviews - general, 1981; F-225-1-0-0-38 (Archival box - standard 225-3)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-2-3-0-13.
  - Graduate requirements - extended essays, 1981 - 1982; F-225-1-0-0-39 (Archival box - standard 225-3)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-5-0-0-2.
  - Graduate regulations, 1981 - 1989; F-225-1-0-0-40 (Archival box - standard 225-3)
  - Foreign students - immigration, 1982 - 1986; F-225-1-0-0-41 (Archival box - standard 225-3)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-2-3-0-8.
  - Progress reports, 1983; F-225-1-0-0-42 (Archival box - standard 225-3)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-2-3-0-26.
  - Graduate Student statistics, 1983 - 1985; F-225-1-0-0-43 (Archival box - standard 225-3)
  - Examining committees and external examiners - procedures, 1983 - 1985; F-225-1-0-0-44 (Archival box - standard 225-3)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-2-3-0-6.
  - Graduate Studies handbook, 1985; F-225-1-0-0-45 (Archival box - standard 225-3)
    Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-12-0-0-17.
  - Graduate part-time fees, vol. 1, 1985 - 1989; F-225-1-0-0-46 (Archival box - standard 225-3)
  - Graduate part-time fees, vol. 2, 1985 - 1989; F-225-1-0-0-47 (Archival box - standard 225-4)
  - Origin of graduate students, 1985 - 1991; F-225-1-0-0-48 (Archival box - standard 225-4)
    Restricted in part
  - Graduate Student Centre, vol. 1, 1985 - 1992; F-225-1-0-0-49 (Archival box - standard 225-4)
  - Graduate Student Centre, vol. 2, 1985 - 1992; F-225-1-0-0-50 (Archival box - standard 225-4)
  - Dean of Graduate Studies Report to Senate, 1986; F-225-1-0-0-51 (Archival box - standard 225-4)
  - TSSU negotiations, 1986 - 1987; F-225-1-0-0-52 (Archival box - standard 225-4)
  - Enrollment statistics, 1986 - 1988; F-225-1-0-0-53 (Archival box - standard 225-4)
  - Dean of Graduate Studies Report to Senate, 1987; F-225-1-0-0-54 (Archival box - standard 225-4)
  - Enrollment statistics, 1988 - 1989; F-225-1-0-0-55 (Archival box - standard 225-4)
  - T.A. Day, 1988 - 1989; F-225-1-0-0-56 (Archival box - standard 225-4)
  - Fees, 1988 - 1990; F-225-1-0-0-57 (Archival box - standard 225-4)
  - Graduate Scholarships Day, 1989; F-225-1-0-0-58 (Archival box - standard 225-5)
  - Western Canadian Graduate Deans short course fund (KAP and KIP), 1989 - 1990; F-225-1-0-0-59 (Archival box - standard 225-5)
  - Graduate program development survey, 1989 - 1990; F-225-1-0-0-60 (Archival box - standard 225-5)
  - Graduate Scholarships Day, 1990; F-225-1-0-0-61 (Archival box - standard 225-5)
  - Physics 130/131 [taught by B. Clayman], 1990; F-225-1-0-0-62 (Archival box - standard 225-5)
  - Task Force on Quality of Service, vol. 1, 1990 - 1991; F-225-1-0-0-63 (Archival box - standard 225-5)
  - Task Force on Quality of Service, vol. 2, 1990 - 1991; F-225-1-0-0-64 (Archival box - standard 225-5)
  - T.A. Day, 1990 - 1991; F-225-1-0-0-65 (Archival box - standard 225-5)
  - Supervision and teaching, 1990 - 1992; F-225-1-0-0-66 (Archival box - standard 225-5)
  - Graduate program committee survey, 1990 - 1993; F-225-1-0-0-67 (Archival box - standard 225-5)
  - Graduate Scholarships Day, 1991; F-225-1-0-0-68 (Archival box - standard 225-5)
  - Graduate Studies newsletter, 1991; F-225-1-0-0-69 (Archival box - standard 225-5)
  - Graduate Studies fact book, 1991; F-225-1-0-0-70 (Archival box - standard 225-5)
  - Graduate Studies Day, 1991; F-225-1-0-0-71 (Archival box - standard 225-5)
  - Graduate Studies handbook, 1991 - 1992; F-225-1-0-0-72 (Archival box - standard 225-6)
  - Graduate Studies Day, 1992; F-225-1-0-0-73 (Archival box - standard 225-6)
  - Graduate Awards Day, 1992; F-225-1-0-0-74 (Archival box - standard 225-6)
  - Origins of graduate students, 1992; F-225-1-0-0-75 (Archival box - standard 225-6)
  - Graduate Studies fact book, 1992; F-225-1-0-0-76 (Archival box - standard 225-6)
  - Strategic Planning 2001 (Challenge 2001), 1993; F-225-1-0-0-77 (Archival box - standard 225-6)
  - Physics 233/234 [taught by B. Clayman], 1993; F-225-1-0-0-78 (Archival box - standard 225-6)
  - Graduate survey, 1997 - 1998; F-225-1-0-0-79 (Archival box - standard 225-6)
- Correspondence, 1969 - 1992; F-225-2; 51 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to the Dean of Graduate Studies correspondence with Graduate Program Chairs and academic departments about various issues relating to graduate studies at the university. Also included is correspondence sent and received by the Associate Dean of Graduate Studies, correspondence with the Simon Fraser Student Society and the University Council of British Columbia. Records include correspondence and working papers, minutes, and reports.
  Simon Fraser Student Society; Universities Council of British Columbia
  - General correspondence, 1969 - 1990; F-225-2-1; 4 cm of textual records
    - Dean's correspondence - miscellaneous topics, 1969 - 1979; F-225-2-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 225-6)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-2-3-0-3.
    - University Council of B.C., 1977; F-225-2-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 225-6)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-2-3-0-35.
    - Associate Dean - general, 1977 - 1982; F-225-2-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 225-6)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-2-1-0-4.
    - Simon Fraser Student Society - graduate issues, 1987 - 1990; F-225-2-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 225-6)
  - Graduate Program Chairs correspondence, 1985 - 1992; F-225-2-2; 6 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence and reports, 1985 - 1989; F-225-2-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 225-7)
    - Correspondence and reports, 1990; F-225-2-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 225-7)
    - Correspondence and reports, 1991; F-225-2-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 225-7)
    - Correspondence and reports, vol. 1, 1992; F-225-2-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 225-7)
    - Correspondence and reports, vol. 2, 1992; F-225-2-2-0-5 (Archival box - standard 225-7)
  - Graduate Program Chairs Special Arrangements correspondence, 1988 - 1991; F-225-2-3; 6 cm of textual records
    - Special arrangements correspondence and reports, 1988; F-225-2-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 225-7)
    - Special arrangements correspondence and reports, 1989; F-225-2-3-0-2 (Archival box - standard 225-7)
    - Special arrangements correspondence and reports, 1990; F-225-2-3-0-3 (Archival box - standard 225-7)
    - Special arrangements correspondence and reports, vol. 1, 1991; F-225-2-3-0-4 (Archival box - standard 225-7)
    - Special arrangements correspondence and reports, vol. 2, 1991; F-225-2-3-0-5 (Archival box - standard 225-7)
  - Departmental correspondence, 1971 - 1991; F-225-2-4; 34 cm of textual records
    - Centre for Environmental Health, 1971 - 1972; F-225-2-4-0-1 (Archival box - standard 225-8)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-2-1-0-52.
    - P.S.A., 1972 - 1975; F-225-2-4-0-2 (Archival box - standard 225-8)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-2-1-0-45.
    - Sociology/Anthropology, 1974 - 1978; F-225-2-4-0-3 (Archival box - standard 225-8)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-2-1-0-46.
    - Department of Languages, Literatures and Linguistics, 1976 - 1989; F-225-2-4-0-4 (Archival box - standard 225-8)
    - Department of Communications, 1980; F-225-2-4-0-5 (Archival box - standard 225-8)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-21-2-3-0-4.
    - School of Engineering Science, 1980 - 1991; F-225-2-4-0-6 (Archival box - standard 225-8)
    - Gerontology, 1981 - 1989; F-225-2-4-0-7 (Archival box - standard 225-8)
    - Political Science, 1981 - 1991; F-225-2-4-0-8 (Archival box - standard 225-8)
    - Sociology/Anthropology, 1981 - 1991; F-225-2-4-0-9 (Archival box - standard 225-8)
    - Resource and Environmental Management, 1981 - 1991; F-225-2-4-0-10 (Archival box - standard 225-8)
    - Faculty of Business Administration, 1982 - 1991; F-225-2-4-0-11 (Archival box - standard 225-8)
    - Computing Science, 1982 - 1991; F-225-2-4-0-12 (Archival box - standard 225-8)
    - Economics, 1983 - 1990; F-225-2-4-0-13 (Archival box - standard 225-9)
    - History, 1983 - 1990; F-225-2-4-0-14 (Archival box - standard 225-9)
    - Criminology, 1983 - 1991; F-225-2-4-0-15 (Archival box - standard 225-9)
    - Mathematics and Statistics, 1983 - 1991; F-225-2-4-0-16 (Archival box - standard 225-9)
    - Chemistry, 1983 - 1991; F-225-2-4-0-17 (Archival box - standard 225-9)
    - Archaeology, 1983 - 1991; F-225-2-4-0-18 (Archival box - standard 225-9)
    - Biological Sciences, 1983 - 1991; F-225-2-4-0-19 (Archival box - standard 225-9)
    - English, 1983 - 1991; F-225-2-4-0-20 (Archival box - standard 225-9)
    - Education, 1983 - 1991; F-225-2-4-0-21 (Archival box - standard 225-9)
    - Kinesiology, 1983 - 1991; F-225-2-4-0-22 (Archival box - standard 225-10)
    - Psychology, 1983 - 1991; F-225-2-4-0-23 (Archival box - standard 225-10)
    - Philosophy, 1985 - 1986; F-225-2-4-0-24 (Archival box - standard 225-10)
    - Continuing Studies, 1985 - 1987; F-225-2-4-0-25 (Archival box - standard 225-10)
    - Physics, 1985 - 1990; F-225-2-4-0-26 (Archival box - standard 225-10)
    - Geography, 1985 - 1991; F-225-2-4-0-27 (Archival box - standard 225-10)
    - Communication, 1985 - 1991; F-225-2-4-0-28 (Archival box - standard 225-10)
    - Master of Pest Management program, 1987 - 1990; F-225-2-4-0-29 (Archival box - standard 225-10)
    - Contemporary Arts, 1987 - 1991; F-225-2-4-0-30 (Archival box - standard 225-10)
    - French, 1989 - 1991; F-225-2-4-0-31 (Archival box - standard 225-10)
    - Women's Studies, 1989 - 1991; F-225-2-4-0-32 (Archival box - standard 225-10)